Tatenda Mushayakarara

CYBERSECURITY ENGINEER · SOFTWARE ENGINEER

32 4th Crescent Warren Park 1, Harare, Zimbabwe

① (+263)778 726 595 | ⊠ tatalmondmush@gmail.com | otatmush | o tatmush | o tatalmondmush

Summary

I have 2+ years of experience in software engineering as a full stack developer on python and javascript. I also have 1+ years of experience in cybersecurity and audit. I am interested in cybersecurity, devops or software engineering aligned positions that offer opportunities to utilize my skills whilst learning new technologies and tools.

Work Experience____

Zimbabwe Electricity Transmission and Distribution Company

Mutare, Zimbabwe

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, DEVOPS ENGINEER

Jan. 2021 - Oct 2021

- Designed and developed Django microservices.
- Developed REST API's with Django.
- Developed React-Native mobile applications consuming API's.
- Building CI/CD processes for application deployment.
- Architecting and building infrastructure and tooling across web and mobile development.

Capesso Harare, Zimbabwe

INFRASTRUCTURE ENGINEER, SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, BUSINESS ANALYST

Jan. 2020 – Dec. 2020

- Managed oracle cloud infrastructure Oracle Cloud Infrastructure.
 - Monitoring and optimizing cloud services.
 - O Automating infrastructure migration to cloud environments.
 - O Implementing cloud governance, build, deployment and monitoring standards for clients.
- Implemented Oracle Financial Services Analytical Applications Liquidity Risk Management (OFSAA-LRM) at CABS
- Implemented Model Calibration for OFSAA-IFRS9
- Business consultant for ERP solutions NetSuite, Microsoft Dynamics Nav, Odoo.
- Developed Odoo Paynow module.
- Developed Etoni e-commerce website and mobile apps (Play store & App store)

Zimbabwe Electricity Transmission and Distribution Company

Mutare, Zimbabwe

Jan. 2019 - Aug 2019

System support.

• Setup and deployed a LAN GitLab server.

Telco Harare, Zimbabwe

INTERN Aug. 2018 – Dec 20

- Implemented vehicle tracking system with Mikrotik for tracking, php backend and open street map.
- Customized Odoo modules using python and javascript.
- Networking.

Zimbabwe Centre for High Performance Computing

Harare, Zimbabwe

INTERN

INTERN

Mar. 2018 – Jul 2018

• Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning Research.

Education

Harare Institute of Technology

Harare, Zimbabwe

BTECH (HONS) INFORMATION SECURITY AND ASSURANCE

2016 - 2020

Grade First Class Honours Degree

Certifications

Oracle BI Foundation Suite 11g Solution Engineer Specialist

USA

ORACLE

2020

Java Course

Zimbabwe/ USA

MUZINDA HUB/TREEHOUSE

2015 – 2016

Ubuntu Business Certificate

Zimbabwe/ USA

MUZINDA HUB/TREEHOUSE

2015 - 2016

Honours & Awards

- Awarded Degree with Distinction.
- Awarded the Vice Chancellor's Price for the Best Graduating Student in Information Security and Assurance.
- Awarded the HIT Book Prize for the Best Capstone Design Project.
- Awarded the HIT Book Prize for the Best Graduating Student in Technopreneurship.

Projects

Capstone Design Project Blockchain Land Registry System

Harare, Zimbabwe

Source code: www.github.com/tatmush/Blockchain-Land-Registry

Demo video: shorturl.at/vEIM9

A land registry system that harnesses the properties of Ethereum blockchain and solidity language. Land is issued as a non-fungible ERC721 token on the blockchain. Ownership transference is recorded on the blockchain. A django server provides metadata for the system.

HIT 200 Secure Email System

Harare, Zimbabwe

Source code: www.github.com/evermoreg/digitalFile

A secure email system using hybrid cryptography (AES + RSA) built with Hybrid Crypto JS and a Flask web framework backend.

Hasi yaNoku Harare, Zimbabwe

Demo video: https://youtu.be/S8KBK--Alcs

An implementation of artificial intelligence face recognition model to recognize faces in a popular drama Wadiwa Wepamoyo characters.

Tomato Leaf Disease Detection using AI Model

Harare, Zimbabwe

Source Code: https://github.com/tatmush/tomato-leaf-disease-detection

An implementation of a deep learning model to diagnose tomato diseases from leaves.

Program Committees	
President Cybercrypts	Harare, Zimbabwe
	2019 – 2020
References	
AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST	